Last update: 5/15/2022



Kourosh Ahmadzadeh Ataei

Gmail | in Github | in Linkedin

Personal Data

Address: No.226, Dehkhoda 7 St., Piruzi Blvd., Mashhad, IRAN.

Mobile: +989036928421

Date of birth: December 19, 1996. (25 years)

Place of birth: Ferdows, IRAN

Education

Ferdowsi University of Mashhad (FUM)

Bachelor of Computer Engineering GPA 15.56/20 (3.31 GPA)

• Last 2 years GPA is 16.59 (3.52 GPA)

 Relevant Coursework: Data Mining – Algorithm Design - Database - Information Retrieval -Artificial Intelligence – Web Development - Data communication – Multimedia systems - Data Structures

Areas of Interests

Computer Vision, Deep learning, Machine learning, Web development, Rest API, Blockchain, Software engineering, Information Retrieval, Data Mining

Experience

Junior Software Engineer, Co-Founder Al Trader startup (Aran Accelerator)

I am responsible for:

- Develop platform base on python
- Develop telegram bot for front
- Work with MySQL

Main achievement:

- Acquire team management Teamwork
- Learn and Implement Pattern Designs

- Sysadmin for server side
- Product manager
- Some experiences in product manager
- Participation in Al Project

Mashhad, IRAN

Sep. 2016 - Sep. 2021

Jun. 2022 – Feb. 2022

Last update: 5/15/2022

R&D Developer Jun. 2022 – Feb. 2022

Green Render Startup (Aran Accelerator)

I am responsible for:

Configure render farm - multi-GPUs

Main achievement:

 learn server-side commands and bash script(ubuntu-centos) Work with PostgreSQL

• learn research and development

Swift Developer Intern

Jul. 2020 - Sep. 2020

Part software

I am responsible for:

 Develop IOS applications based on swift and objective-c

Main achievement:

- Learn advance GIT
- Learn swift and IOS development

- Learn swift and XCode
- Do tasks and small project

Selected Projects

Work

Teamus website Feb. 2022 – Present

Developed a web application for team and persons CVs & Resumes

- Based on Django python
- App provides team creation and write their CVs for customers
- Cryptocurrency bot API

Apr. 2022 – Present

Develop an API for cryptocurrency bots

- Based on Django rest framework
- App provides strategies and auto trading for customers with purchase plans

Academic

Mstpd UI
Winter 2020

Data communication, Prof.A. Hosseini, FUM

- Implemented a CLI for Multiple Spanning Tree Protocol Daemon project with configure and installation on Ubuntu based on python
- Optimization on TF-IDF recommender system

Fall 2020

Basics of information retrieval and web search, Prof.F.Ensan, FUM.

 Implemented an optimization on classical TF-IDF algorithm and proposed adaptive weight of position of word algorithm based on TF-IDF

Last update: 5/15/2022

Network security API

Winter 2019

Fundamentals of Secure Computing, Prof.H.Amintoosi, FUM

Implemented an API with Django Rest API for check ports, show user logs, Token
Authentication System, check available website user requests, DDoS prevention

• <u>Charity website</u> Fall 2019

Principles of Database Design, Prof.B.behkamal, FUM

 Implemented a free food distribution web application for charities and restaurant based on PHP and MySQL.

• <u>Air Hockey</u> Winter 2016

Advanced Programming, Prof.A.Nouri Baygi, FUM

o JavaFx game application with AI agent

Skills

Languages: Python, familiar with SQL, Solidity, Html, CSS, Java, Swift, bash script, Redis

Libraries: NumPy, Pandas, Web3, Socket, Multithreading, Django, Django REST framework, scrapy,

requests

Technologies: WordPress, Git, PyCharm, Google Colab, XCode, CEH, MVC, Design Patterns, Scrum, fast

API, Telegram bot, photoshop

Languages: English: Upper Intermediate, Persian: Native

About Me

I learned all of my big major of these skills independently although I am **team player** and I willing to **teamwork**. I am **flexible**, **punctual**, **diligent**, **ethical**, **loyal** and **accountable** at work and learn **quickly**. Learning new languages and frameworks enable me to research and develop more and more.